Finding Aid for Arthur J. Tuttle Papers 1849-1958
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Office Files
  - 1921-1925
    - Department of Justice Circulars (Box 23)
    - Department of Justice, Washington (Box 23)
    - Detroit Bar Association (Box 23)
    - Detroit Community Trust (Box 23)
    - Dictaphone Sales Corp. (Box 23)
    - District Judges who acknowledged receipt of blank referees report (Box 23)
    - Dyer Act (Box 23)
    - E-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - F-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Federal Building Changes (Box 23)
    - Federal Business Association (Box 23)
    - Ford vs. Newberry Senate Contest (Box 23)
    - G-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Grand Jurors March 1919 (Box 23)
    - Grand Jurors October 1922 (Box 23)
    - H-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Handwriting experts (Box 23)
    - Hicks, Hon. Xenophon (Box 23)
    - Hickenlooper, Hon. Smith (Box 23)
    - I-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Immigration inspector (Box 23)
    - Immigration matters (Box 23)
    - Internal revenue matters (Box 23)
      (Relates details of investigation of break-in to agent's evidence cabinet and other courthouse thefts. Note that the IRS enforced liquor and narcotics laws during this period)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 23)
    - J-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Jones, Hon. Paul (Box 23)
    - Judge, Additional (Box 23)
      (Includes compiled statistics about caseloads, backlog, etc. and input from important Detroit businessmen, such as Henry Ford, who advocated for an additional judge)
    - Judges' Salaries, 2 folders (Box 23)
      (Tuttle marshals arguments to increase federal judge's salaries)
    - Judgeship Western District of Michigan (Box 23)
      (Interesting political discussion of backing different candidates. Also a report from Tuttle to Denison about the American Law Institute's Congress to create the Restatement of Contracts.)
    - Judicial Robes (Box 23)
      (Prior to the twenties, federal judges did not wear robes. This file contains judges' correspondence regarding the growing acceptance of robes, as well as a fabric sample)
    - Jury Commission (Box 23)
    - K-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Killits, Hon. John M. (Box 23)
    - Knappen, Hon. Loyal E. (Box 23)
    - L-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - Mc-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
      (Congressman Clarence J. McLeod)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
      (Congressman Earl C. Michener)
    - Marshal, U.S. (Box 24)
    - Michigan Dormitories Corp. (Box 24)
      (U. of M. dormitory construction)
    - N-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
      (Senators Harry S. New and Knute Nelson)
    - Naturalization Matters (Box 24)
    - Naturalization Officer (Box 24)
      (M.J. Kilsdonk, birth of naturalization bureaucracy in federal court)
    - O-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - O'Meara, Dennis H. (Box 24)
      (Blueprint of O'Meara's design for new Federal building)
    - P-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - Parole and Pardon (Box 24)
      (Congressmen Elmer H. Geran, Isaac Siegel)
    - Pathfinders of America (Box 24)
    - Police, Detroit, Department of (Box 24)
    - Post Office, Detroit (Box 24)
    - Prohibition Department, 3 folders (Box 24)
      (Michigan Attorney General Merlin Wiley, Detroit Prohibition Directors James R. Davis, A.C. Graham and Royal E. Decker, U.S. Attorney General H.M. Daugherty, Assistant U.S. Attorney General Mabel Walker Willebrandt, Congressman Louis C. Crampton, Detroit Police Commissioner James W. Inches, U.S. Prohibition Commissioner Roy Haynes. Includes newspaper clippings, printed matter, tips from the public, correspondence.)
    - Q-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - R-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - Raymond, Hon. Fred M. (Box 24)
    - Reformatories (Box 24)
    - Ross, Hon. John W. (Box 24)
    - S-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - Sayres, William S., Jr., Standing Master (Box 24)
      (Letter dated April 16, 1925 which describes reforms for the office Tuttle and Sayres had agreed to. Sayres had been gambling in the stock market on the margin and had acquired a huge amount of debt.)
    - Secret Service (Box 24)
    - Simons, Hon. Charles (Box 24)
    - T-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
      (Supreme Court Justice William H. Taft)
    - Traverse Jury, November Term 1920 (Box 24)
      (Juror's excuses)
    - Traverse Jury, May Term 1923 (Box 24)
    - Tuttle, A.J. Reimbursement (Box 24)
    - U-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 24)
    - U.S. Attorney, 2 folders (Box 24)
      (Delos G. Smith, Frederick L. Eaton, J. Earl Davis, John E. Kinnane 1925 criminal calendar)
    - V-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 25)
    - Van Dyke, William (Box 25)
      (AJT long letter regarding dissatisfaction with bankruptcy receivership procedure)
    - W-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 25)
      (Senator Thomas J. Walz, Judges D.C. Westenhaver, Dual West)
    - Western District Matters (Box 25)
      (Grand Rapids U.S. Attorney Edwin J. Bowman, Congressman W. Frank James, Judge Clarence W. Sessions)
    - Western Union Telegraph Co. (Box 25)
      (Contains telegram: Bill introduced. Congress provided Additional District. Judge Eastern Michigan Advise Department your views. Daugherty)
    - Warren, Charles Beecher (Box 25)
      (Senator George Wharton Pepper)
    - X-Y-Z-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 25)
  - 1926-June, 1929
    - A-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 25)
      (Harry B. Anderson)
    - Anonymous Letters (Box 25)
    - Attorney General (Box 25)
      (John G. Sargent, John Marshall, Mabel Walker Willebrandt, Congressman Roy O. Woodruff)
    - B-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 25)
    - Bankruptcy
      - Administration of Estates (Box 25)
      - Attorneys Fees (Box 25)
      - Attorneys Meetings
        (Includes transcripts of meetings of Detroit bankruptcy attorneys)
        - 1926 (Box 25)
        - 1927-February 1928 (Box 25)
        - March 1928-April 1928 (Box 25)
        - May 1928-August 1928 (Box 25)
      - Auctioneers (Box 25)
      - Audits (Box 25)
      - Bonds and Depositories (Box 25)
      - Cases delayed by litigation in other courts (Box 25)
      - Chimovitz Bros., Bankrupt (Box 25)
        (Letter from Tuttle to the bankruptcy trustees regarding corruption among the bankruptcy attorneys)
      - Conference of Referees 1926 (Box 25)
      - Correspondence with judges (Box 25)
        (Judge Learned Hand, and many other Federal judges thanking Tuttle for sending them copies of his District Court Bankruptcy Rules)
      - Fleischmann, Simon (Box 25)
      - Force, Charles H., Bankrupt (Box 25)
        (Son of a Tuttle's friend wants to be paid a higher than average fee for inventorying a bankruptcy estate.)
      - General Bankruptcy Matters (Box 25)
      - James Roach Co., Bankrupt (Box 25)
        (Very interesting letter of complaint about the bankruptcy trustee's treatment of a female attorney. Tuttle's daughters were in college at this time and presumably planning their legal careers. Attorney Bessie McDonald apparently saw Tuttle as a supporter of women lawyers)
      - James Schussler & Co., Bankrupt (Box 25)
      - John J. Davis & Sons Co., Bankrupt (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous cases (Box 25)
      - National Association of Referees in Bankruptcy (Box 26)
      - Office Administration (Box 26)
      - Poll, Leo, Bankrupt (Box 26)
      - Referees Reports 1926-1927 (Box 26)
      - Referees Reports 1928-1929 (Box 26)
      - Report of Examiners 1926 (Box 26)
      - Rosenberg & Gingold (Box 26)
        (Indictments of attorneys for violation of bankruptcy law, U.S. Attorney Delos Smith accuses trustee George Marston of inappropriate partisanship)
      - Rules (Box 26)
      - Supreme Court Justices --Re: Bankruptcy Rules (Box 26)
      - Salaries (Box 26)
    - Baumes Laws (Box 26)
      (Newspaper clippings)
    - C-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 26)
      (Judge William Clark, Senator James Couzens, Congressman Louis C. Cramton, Commissioner U.S. Court of Claims, John A. Elmore)
    - Charge to Jury, 4 folders (Box 26)
      (Forms for jury instructions)
    - Circuit Court of Appeals 6th Circuit Dockets, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Circuit Court of Appeals, General (Box 26)
    - Clerk-Bay City (Box 26)
    - Clerk-Circuit Court of Appeals (Box 26)
    - Clerk-Detroit (Box 26)
    - Corn borer extermination (Box 26)
      (AJT detailed follow-up of a juror's complaint about agricultural examiners not doing their jobs)
    - Court calendars (Box 26)
    - Custodians (Box 26)
    - D-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 26)
      (Judge Maurice H. Donahue)
    - Dawkins, Hon. Ben C. (Box 26)
    - Denison, Hon. Arthur C. 1926 (Box 26)
      (Chief Justice of the 6th Circuit)
    - Department of Justice (Box 26)
      (Asst. U.S. Supt. of Prisons H. C. Heckman, Assts. Attorney General Mabel Walker Willebrandt, John Marshall, Charles P. Sisson, Chief Attorney of DOJ, H.S. Ridgely, Supt. Federal Institution for Women, Mary Harris, Acting Attorney General Herman J. Galloway, Attorney General William D. Mitchell)
    - E-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 26)
    - F-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 26)
    - Federal Business Association (Box 27)
    - G-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Prof. Herbert F. Goodrich, Judge John J. Gore)
    - H-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Judges Xenophon Hicks, Smith Hickenlooper)
    - Hudson, Congressman Grant M. re: Session of Court at Flint (Box 27)
    - Hutcheson, Joseph C. and Hastings H. Hart -- County Jails (Box 27)
    - I-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Immigration (Box 27)
    - Income tax on judge's salaries (Box 27)
      (Audit of Tuttle for 1925-1927 Detroit Collector Fred L. Woodworth)
    - J-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Congressman Albert Johnson)
    - Judge, Additional (Box 27)
      (Judges Morris A. Soper, Samuel G. Houghton, John W. Warrington, Congressman Earl C. Michener)
    - Judges Salaries (Box 27)
      (Judges Charles C. Simons, Joseph Buffington, A.C. Denison, Congressmen Roy O. Woodruff, Bird J. Vincent, Louis C. Cramton, Joseph L. Hooper, Grant M. Hudson, W. Frank James, John C. Ketcham, J.C. McLaughlin, Clarence McLeod, Carl E. Mapes, Earl C. Michener, F.W. Scott, John B. Sosnowski, Senator James Couzens, Mich. State Bar Officials, Wade Millis, and Herbert F. Goodrich)
    - Judges, Visiting (Box 27)
      (Judges H.B. Anderson, John J. Gore, Charles I. Dawson, John M. Killits, Xenophon Hicks, A.C. Denison, Benson W. Hough, Smith Hickenlooper)
    - Jury Commissioners (Box 27)
    - K-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Judges John M. Killits, John C. Knox)
    - L-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Library, In re (Box 27)
      (Judge A.C. Denison)
    - Mc-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Congressman Clarence McLeod)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Judges Charles H. Moorman, Congressman Earl C. Michener)
    - Moinet, Hon. E.J.-Courtroom and Chambers (Box 27)
      (Sen. James Couzens)
    - N-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Narcotic -- General (Box 27)
    - Naturalization Director, Detroit (Box 27)
    - Naturalization, General (Box 27)
    - O-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Judge Merrill E. Otis)
    - P-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Pathfinders of America (Box 27)
    - Prohibition Dept.-Detroit and Bay City (Box 27)
      (Agents Thomas Brennan and Edwin A. Grove, Thomas E. Stone, Nelson Huron, James Reid, Charles Zaeski)
    - Prohibition -- General (Box 27)
      (Wayne B. Wheeler of Anti-Saloon League of America, many letters with tips from the public)
    - Probation Officer (Box 27)
      (Dean Mortimer E. Cooley, Attorney General John G. Sargent, Judges Clyde I. Webster, Harry B. Keidan, Detroit Mayor John W. Smith)
    - Questionnaire -- Survey of Federal Employees (Box 27)
    - R-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Ray Jewelry Co. Lease (Box 27)
      (Tuttle discovered a booking joint in back of restaurant where he regularly ate. He corresponded with the police commissioner to see that it was prosecuted, but the bookies were tipped off before the squad got there.)
    - Raymond, Hon. Fred M. (Box 27)
    - Requisitions and Vouchers (Box 27)
      (Travel expenses etc.)
    - S-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Judge Charles Simons)
    - Sayres, Wm. S., Jr. Standing Master (Box 27)
    - Simons, Hon. Charles C. (Box 27)
    - Statistics-Citizenship Status of Criminal Defendants (Box 27)
    - T-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
      (Chief Justice William Howard Taft)
    - U-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 27)
    - U.S. Attorney -- Bay City (Box 27)
    - U.S. Attorney-Detroit (Box 27)
      (Delos Smith, John R. Watkins)
    - U.S. Commissioner (Box 27)
      (Frank Q. Quinn, J. Stanley Hurd, John Simpson, Frank R. Schnell)
    - U.S. Marshal (Box 28)
    - V-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 28)
      (Senator A.H. Vandenberg)
    - W-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 28)
      (Congressman Roy O. Woodruff, Asst. Attorney General, Mabel Walker Willebrandt)
    - Westerhaver, Hon. D.C. (Box 28)
  - July 1929-July, 1933
    - A-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 28)
      (Congressman George G. Sadowski, Asst. Attorney Gen. Charles P. Sisson, Mich. Atty. Gen. Wilber M. Brucker)
    - Additional Judge (Box 28)
      (Senators James Couzens, George W. Norris, Congressman Earl C. Michener)
    - Anonymous Letters (Box 28)
    - Attorney General (Box 28)
      (Asst. Charles P. Sisson)
    - B-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 28)
      (Profs. E. Blythe Stason, Henry M. Bates, Judges John P. Barnes, Frank P. Bohn. In a letter to George E. Brand, Tuttle defends his continued use of West's Publishing instead of Commercial Clearing House to publish his decisions)
    - Banks and Depositors (Statement by A.J.T.) (Box 28)
    - Bankruptcy
      - Administration of Estates (Box 28)
      - Attorney's Meetings (Box 28)
      - Bankruptcy Act (Box 28)
        (Referee Paul King)
      - Bankruptcy Cases -- Miscellaneous (Box 28)
      - Beals, John, Bankrupt (Box 28)
      - Depositories, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
        (5 folders of 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
        (Folder 6 of 6)
      - National Assn. Of Referees in Bankruptcy (Box 29)
      - Requisitions and Reports
        - July 1929-June 1930 (Box 29)
        - June 1930 Audit (Box 29)
        - July-December 1930 (Box 29)
        - January-June 1931 (Box 29)
        - July-December 1931 (Box 29)
        - January-June 1932 (Box 29)
        - July-December 1932 (Box 29)
        - January-July 1933 (Box 29)
      - Union Guardian Trust Co. (Box 29)
      - Statistics June 1932 (Box 29)
    - C-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 29)
      (Gov. William A. Comstock, Judge George A. Carpenter)
    - Calendars (Box 29)
      (Court of Appeals, Admiralty Docket, Equity and Law Cases)
    - Clerk-Bay City (Box 29)
      (Clarence Petit)
    - Clerk-Detroit (Box 29)
    - Commission: Inquiry into the Price of Milk, 2 folders (Box 29)
      (Gov. Wilber M. Brucker, Commissioner Herbert E. Powell, Judge Ira W. Jayne, Tax Collector, Fred L. Woodworth, Professor W.O. Hedrick, Harvey Campbell of Detroit Board of Commerce, Mrs. James E. Hancock, Senator Peter B. Lennon, James N. McBride, Dr. W.O. Hedrick)
    - Court Crier, Re: Appointment of (Box 29)
    - Court Decision Reporters (Box 29)
      (Discussion of how West Publishing secured Tuttle's cooperation in publishing his opinions)
    - Court Rules, New (Box 29)
      (Edson R. Sunderland, of U of M law school, Judge Fred M. Raymond)
    - Custodian (Box 29)
    - D-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 29)
    - Denison, Hon. A.C. (Box 29)
    - Department of Justice, Washington, D.C. (Box 30)
      (Asst. Atty General Charles P. Sisson)
    - Department of Justice, Rulings, etc. (Box 30)
    - E-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
    - Employment (Box 30)
    - F-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
    - Federal Building, Detroit, New (Box 30)
    - Federal Building, Bay City, New (Box 30)
    - G-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
    - H-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
      (Judges George P. Hahn, Samuel G. Houghton, Smith Hickenlooper, Congressman Grant M. Hudson)
    - I-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
    - J-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
      (Judge Paul Jones)
    - Jurors (Box 30)
    - Jury, Grand October 1930 Bay City (Box 30)
    - Jury, Traverse October 1930 Bay City (Box 30)
    - K-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
      (Judges William S. Kenyon, John C. Knox, Frank H. Kerrigan; letter from Paul H. King regarding nominating Tuttle to the Supreme Court upon Justice Holme's resignation)
    - Judges (Federal) (Box 30)
      (Tuttle's speech at Judge Ernest A. O'Brien's induction)
    - L-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
      (Michigan Commissioner of Labor and Industry Isabel Larwill, poem by Tuttle to his jurors about how they will get to play in Irish Hills but he will not)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
      (Chair, Michigan Women's Organization for National Prohibition Reform, Elsie C. Mershon (re: bootleggers in northern Michigan), Judge Guy A. Miller; Congressmen Earl C. Michener, Clarence J. McLeod, Bird J. Vincent; Mayor of Mt. Morris J.K. Mahoney, Willard J. Banyon of Michigan Crime Commission (re: crime statistics in the district), L.C. Marshall of Johns Hopkins Law School (re: uniform crime statistics))
    - Moinet, Hon. Edward J. (Box 30)
    - Moorman, Charles H. (Box 30)
      (now circuit judge of Louisille, Kentucky)
    - N-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
    - National Commission for Law Observance and Enforcement (Box 30)
      (Newspaper clippings, Judges William S. Kenyon, Joseph C. Hutcheson, Jr., Joseph C. Hutcheson, Jr., Commissioner George W. Wickersham, Dean of U. of Mich. Law School, Henry M. Bates)
    - Narcotics Division (Box 30)
    - Naturalization Matters (Box 30)
    - O-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
    - P-Q-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 30)
      (Judges Joseph Buffington (re: statistics), William W. Potter; Pontiac Daily Press)
    - Patent Legislation (Box 30)
    - Pathfinders of America (Box 30)
    - Prisons (Box 30)
      (Director of Federal Bureau of Prisons Sanford Bates)
    - Probation Officers, Selection of (Box 30)
      (Letters from officials with recommendations, applications. Development of a new Prohibition Department, shows growth of federal bureaucracy.)
    - Probation Officer and Service, L. Wallace Hoffman (Box 31)
    - Probation and Parole Matters (Box 31)
      (Chair U.S. Board of Parole Arthur D. Wood; Director Sanford Bates, Supervisor Col. Joel R. Moore of Bureau of Prisons; Ewing Cockrell of United Federation of Justice)
    - Probation and Parole, Printed Material (Box 31)
    - Prohibition Dept. (Box 31)
      (State Senator, Arthur E. Wood)
    - Prohibition Matters, Miscellaneous (Box 31)
      (Tips from public)
    - R-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
    - Redistricting Michigan (Box 31)
      (Senator Arthur H. Vandenberg -- judicial redistricting)
    - Requisitions and Vouchers (Box 31)
      (Travel vouchers)
    - Raymond, Hon. Fred M. (Box 31)
    - S-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
      (Chief Justice Charles E. Hughes, Judges John B. Sanborn, Morris A. Soper, State Senator Chester M. Howell, Senator George W. Norris, U. of M. Prof. Edson R. Sunderland, Sheriff of Ingham Co. Hugh W. Silsby)
    - Simons, Hon. Charles (Box 31)
      (Investigation of a "bankruptcy ring" in Detroit where a lawyer accused prominent bankruptcy lawyers of organizing to extort the bankrupts by making them sign a particular kind of mortgage note.)
    - Statistics, Northern Division (Box 31)
    - T-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
    - Temporary Quarters (Box 31)
      (D.J. Heffernan, Acting Chief Clerk of Department of Justice, Asst. Atty. General Charles P. Sisson)
    - Tuttle/JMB Memos May 1930-May, 1932 (Box 31)
      (Daily memos between AJT and his secretary. Good substitute for a diary to indicate important issues in Tuttle's schedule. Also contain frank, personal assessments of Tuttle's associates.)
    - Tuttle/JMB Memos May 1932-July 1933 (Box 31)
    - U-V-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
      (U.S. Attorney for No. Dist. of Ohio Wilfred J. Mahon, Judge Robert R. Nevin)
    - U.S. Attorney-Bay City (Box 31)
      (Asst. U.S. Atty., Otto J. Manary)
    - U.S. Attorney-Detroit (Box 31)
      (U.S. Atty. John R. Watkins Gregory H. Frederick)
    - U.S. Commissioners (Box 31)
      (Congressmen Louis C. Cramton, Clarence J. McLeod; Senator James Couzens, Port Huron Commissioner Frank R. Schell (bribery allegation, Tuttle accepts his resignation))
    - U.S. Marshal-Bay City (Box 31)
      (Richard LaBelle)
    - U.S. Marshal-Detroit (Box 31)
      (Frank T. Newton, John H. Grogan)
    - W-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
      (Congressmen Roy O. Woodruff, L.C. Wyer)
    - X-Y-Z-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
  - August 1933-July 1937
    - A-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
      (Congressman Louis C. Rabaut)
    - Anonymous (Box 31)
    - Attorney General-Washington (Box 31)
      (Attorney General Homer S. Cummings, and his aide C. E. Stewart)
    - Attorney General, Sentences to custody of (Box 32)
    - B-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 32)
      (U. of M. Law School Dean Henry M. Bates, Congressman Adolph J. Sabath, Pres. Detroit Bar Assn. George E. Brand)
    - Bankruptcy
      - Deposit Funds Suits and Fees Allowed Attorneys (Box 32)
      - Legislation (Box 32)
      - Miscellaneous
        (Referees Paul King and George A. Marston)
        - July-December 1933 (Box 32)
        - January-June 1934 (Box 32)
        - July-December 1934 (Box 32)
        - January-December 1935 (Box 32)
          (Judge H.A. Hollzer
        - January-June 1936 (Box 32)
        - July-December 1936 (Box 32)
      - National Association of Referees in Bankruptcy (Box 32)
      - Office Administration, 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Requisitions and Reports
        - 1933 (Box 32)
        - 1934 (Box 32)
        - January-June 1935 (Box 32)
        - July-December 1935 (Box 32)
        - 1936 (Box 32)
        - 1937 (Box 32)
      - Rules (Box 32)
      - Senate Investigation of Receiverships, 4 folders (Box 32)
        (Tuttle's 52 page letter to Senator W.G. McAdoo)
      - 77-B (Box 33)
    - C-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Clerk of Court-Bay City
      - 1933-1934 (Box 33)
      - 1935 (Box 33)
      - 1936 (Box 33)
      - 1937 (Box 33)
    - Clerk of Court-Detroit (Box 33)
      (Elmer Voorheis, includes his resignation under charge of corruption)
    - Clerk of Court-re: Appointment (Box 33)
    - Conciliation Commissioner (Box 33)
    - Consumers Industries, Inc. (Box 33)
    - Custodians -- Detroit and Bay City (Box 33)
      (W.C. Garred)
    - D-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Department of Justice-Washington (Box 33)
      (FBI Director, J. Edgar Hoover, Special Assts. to Atty. General, Maj. Edgar B. Tolman, Alexander Holtzoff, Pardon Attorney, James A. Finch, Administrative Asst. to Atty. General Charles E. Stewart, Bureau of Prisons Director Sanford Bates)
    - Department of Justice Bureau of Investigation (Box 33)
      (Agents D.L. Nicholson, Wm. Larson)
    - Department of Justice Circulars (Box 33)
    - Disbarment Proceedings (Box 33)
    - E-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
    - F-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
      (Pres. Federal Bar Assoc., Henry Ward Beer; Editor of Federal Writers Project, Harriet Culver, Justice Louis H. Fead)